MAKI HIROSE

maki@makicoding.com | 347-615-1458 | New York, NY

Website: https://www.makicoding.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/makihirose | GitHub: https://github.com/makicoding

SUMMARY

Front End Web Developer with over ten years of visual experience in the Commercial Photography Industry.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, Git, GitHub.

Visual Studio Code, Terminal, Photoshop, Capture One, Photo Mechanic, Lightroom, Bridge, Final Cut Pro, Premiere, Logic Pro, ProTools, Word, Excel, MacOS.

PROJECTS

80's Music Hangman Game | https://github.com/makicoding/Word-Guess-Game | https://makicoding.github.io/Word-Guess-Game

The user has to guess the Artist and there are a total 5 different games with user-optional-playback audio hints. Tools used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

EXPERIENCE

Commercial Photographer - MAKIDIGITAL LLC - New York, NY

2012 - Present

Responsibilities include being a: Business Owner, Commercial Photographer, Retoucher, Videographer, Instagram Vlogger, YouTuber, and Marketer.

Website: Maki Digital .COM (www.makidigital.com)

Clients include: L'Oréal, Maybelline, Diageo, Smirnoff, Tanqueray Gin, IW Harper, JUICE Pharma, Sterling Vineyards, Landor, Colangelo, Grind Espresso Spirit, Califresca, Blade & Bow, Marshall Retail, NY Minute Retail, Fancy Pants Group, JWT... and many more.

Interviewed by Sakura Radio USA, Live On-Air for the talk show "Nama Repo 50 States".

Awards: The Canon Creative Asia Awards | FoundFolios Collection (3 times).

Digital Imaging Specialist - Drive In Studios DI24 - New York, NY

2007 - 2012

Responsibilities include being a: Digital Imaging Specialist and Retoucher on Commercial Photoshoots.

Clients include: IBM, GE, Citibank, Microsoft, Sony, Vodafone, Merck & Co. Inc., Allianz, AstraZeneca, Ikea, Adidas Y-3, Kate Spade, Absolut Vodka, Six Flags, Macy's, Bloomingdale's, Gillette, Food Network, Bravo, Coach, Cosmopolitan... and many more.

Featured on Condé Nast Allure TV and Food Network TV.

MAKI HIROSE

maki@makicoding.com | 347-615-1458 | New York, NY

Website: https://www.makicoding.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/makihirose | GitHub: https://github.com/makicoding

EDUCATION

Columbia University, New York, NY

2019

Columbia Engineering Coding Bootcamp Full Stack Web Development Intensive

Started, led and organized Saturday study group sessions and the Meetup.com group "NYC Columbia Coding Bootcamp Meetup"

New York University, New York, NY

2003 - 2007

Tisch School of the Arts, Department of Photography + Imaging Bachelors of Fine Art in Photography + Imaging

New York University Honors Scholar Founder's Day Award Recipient NYU Tisch School of the Arts Dean's List (2 times)

St. Paul's School, London, UK

LANGUAGES

English, native | Japanese, native

ACTIVITIES

Lead Singer and Electric Guitarist for the Alternative Rock Band: SCREAMER. Live performances include Kenny's Castaways in NYC and 2 Album Releases on Amazon and Spotify including "Screamer One In Ten":

(https://www.amazon.com/One-Ten-Screamer/dp/B0013XQIBS/ref=sr_1_1?keywords=screamer+one+in+ten&qid=1549637003&sr=8-1)

INTERESTS

Portrait Photography, Thinking, Walking, Movies, Being in the Kitchen, Parasailing, Skiing, Circus Shows, Live Rock Music.